Marcel Breuer
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1923-1986, Series 2:; (Boxes 1-6, OV 47; Reels 5708-5717; 5.3 linear feet)
  United States Embassy, London, 1960-1961 (2 letters): from Breuer concerning Jo Yorke and Jane Susannah Yorke
  United States General Services Administration (GSA), 1963-1977 (3 letters)
  United States Government Printing Office, 1947 (2 letters): from Breuer
  United States Information Agency, 1957-1964 (7 letters)
  United States National Commission for UNESCO, 1951 (information for a conference)
  United States Plywood Corporation, 1946 (1 letter)
  United States Postmaster General, 1955 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  United States Selective Service, 1942 (notice of classification)
  United States Social Security Administration, 1956 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Untermeyer, Louis, 1964 (1 letter)
  Urbahn, Max O. (architect), 1965-1975 (2 letters)
  Ustinov, Nadie, undated (1 letter)
  Vachon, Judy and David, undated and 1964 (2 letters)
  Valentin, Kurt (Buchholz Gallery), 1944 (1 letter)
  Valle, Tommaso and Gilberto, undated (1 letter)
  Van Altena, Edward, 1951 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Van den Broek, Professor J. H. (architect), undated (1 letter)
  van der Straeten, Jean (CBR Cimenteries Bruxelles), 1970 (1 letter)
  Van der Wal, Dr. G., undated and 1961-1966 (6 letters)
  Van Doren, Mark, 1963 (2 letters): see also Citizens Committee for a Nuclear Test Ban Treaty
  van Eesteren, C. (architect), 1951 (1 letter)
  van Leer, Oscar, 1970 (1 letter)
  van Westen, J. H., 1960 (1 letter)
  Varèse, Edgard (composer), 1956 (1 letter)
  Vargha, László I., 1967 (2 letters)
  Vecchione, Robert, 1964-1970 (2 letters)
  Véghelyi, Péter (Acta Paediatrica, Hungarian Science Academy), 1963-1972 (5 letters)
  Ventris, Dora (and Michael), undated (1 letter)
  Vergun, Alexei, 1975 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Verlag Girsberger, 1956 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Viasz, Andor Safed ("Bendj"), 1962 (1 letter)
  Vidal, Yves, 1956-1971 (7 letters)
  Vincent, Mr., 1963 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Violich, Francis, 1955 (1 letter)
  Virág, Csaba (Hungarian architect), 1965-1974 (3 letters)
  Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1960 (2 letters)
  Virginia, University of, 1967-1970 (18 letters)
  Vissière, A. (architect), undated (1 letter)
  Visy, Béla, 1957 (1 letter)
  Vitrum magazine (Centro Informazioni e Studi per le Applicazioni del Vetro nell'Edilizia e nell'Arredamento; C.I.S.A.V.), 1955 (1 letter)
  Vogel, George S. (Temple Israel, Cortlandt), 1951 (1 letter)
  Voigt, James D. (Voigt and Fourré, Architects), 1958 (4 letters)
  Volante, Julio C., 1955-1963 (2 letters)
  von Debschitz, Irene, 1935 (1 letter)
  von Erffa, H., 1951-1968 (2 letters)
  von Meyerburg, Henrietta [?], undated (1 letter)
  von Moltke, Wilhelm Viggo, 1946-1958 (4 letters)
  von Segesser, Beat and Francisca, 1968-1975 (1 letter, plus 4 from Breuer)
  Wachsmann, Konrad (architect/designer, General Panel Corporation), 1945-1965 (8 letters): see National Council of American Soviet Friendship, Inc., Architects' Committee
  Wadsworth, Suzanne G., 1975 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Wagner, Martin (Harvard University), 1946 (2 letters)
  Senator Wagner Memorial Dinner, 1965 (1 invitation): from mayor of New York
  Walker and Company, 1966-1967 (2 letters): includes a typescript about Breuer; see also Heyer, Paul O.
  Walker Art Center, Center Arts Council, 1959-1962 (12 letters)
  Walker, H. E. L. (Universal Moulded Products Company, Ltd.), 1943 (1 letter)
  Walker, Ralph (AIA), 1951 (1 letter): from Walter Gropius
  Walker, Vicki, 1968 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Ward, Ernest and Priscilla (Sprague Electric Company), 1946 (2 letters)
  Washington University, St. Louis, Missouri, 1975 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Watson, Arthur K. (U.S. Embassy, Paris), 1970-1972 (2 letters)
  Watson, Thomas, 1970 (1 letter)
  Wattjes, Professor J. G., 1935 (1 letter)
  Webb & Knapp (Canada), Ltd., 1963 (3 letters)
  Weidler, Charlotte (Bauhaus Ausstellung), 1968 (1 letter)
  Weidlinger, Paul, 1946: see Project File for UNESCO
  Weidlinger Associates, 1983-1984 (2 letters)
  Weiner, Paul L., 1950-1966 (2 letters)
  Weinstein, Jerry, 1945 (1 letter)
  William H. Weintraub & Company, Inc., 1943-1947 (3 letters)
  Weiz [?], Tiberio, 1939 (1 letter)
  Weizenblatt, Sprinza, 1946-1963 (20 letters)
  Wenzler, William P. (architect), 1965-1968 (4 letters)
  Weren, Edward C., 1946 (1 letter)
  Werner, Ingrid, 1963 (3 letters)
  Wertz, Mr. (Der Finanzminister des Landes Nordrhein-Westfalen), 1974 (1 letter): from Breuer
  West China Development Corporation, 1947 (1 letter)
  West Coast Stained Shingle Company, 1950 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Westcott and Mapes, Inc. (architects and engineers), 1970 (1 letter)
  Western Arts Association, 1959 (4 letters)
  Western Reserve University, 1958 (5 letters)
  Westport Public Library, 1975 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Wetter, Barbara, 1980 (1 letter): concerns traveling exhibition
  Wheaton, William L. (Pomona College), 1960 (1 letter)
  White, George (architect of the Capitol), 1975 (1 letter): from Breuer
  White House (Letitia Baldridge), 1963 (1 letter): mentions Jacqueline Kennedy
  White, J. G. (Peerless Flooring Company), 1955 (1 letter)
  Whitney, Charles E. (Publications, Inc.), 1954-1956 (2 letters): from Breuer's office
  Whitney Museum of American Art, 1968-1976 (19 letters): 1 from Jean Lipman; 14 from Breuer and a typescript about Alexander Calder
  Who's Who in America, 1947 (2 letters)
  Wieland, Albert, 1963 (1 letter)
  Wiener, Paul Lester and Ingebord, 1944-1955 (3 letters)
  Wiesenfeld, David, 1957 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Wieser, U. P. (Wohnbedarf furniture store), 1959-1960 (3 letters)
  Wigglesworth, Isabella C., 1946 (1 letter)
  Wilcox & Company, 1972 (1 letter)
  Wilder, Hugo, 1946 (1 letter): from E. S. Ferguson
  Wiley, Chuck, 1950 (1 letter)
  Wilhelm, Günter, 1949 (1 letter)
  Wilinski, Erich, 1935 (2 letters)
  Willard, Marian G. ("Viva Villa"; East River Gallery), undated and 1935-1965 (25 letters)
  Williams, Amancio (architect), 1955 (1 letter)
  Williams, Daniel, 1974 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Williams, Peter C., 1956 (1 letter)
  Williams, Preston, 1958 (2 letters)
  Wilson, Dr. and Mrs. Julius Lane, 1965 (1 letter)
  Wilson, June P. (Mrs. Kenneth Wilson), 1968 (1 letter)
  Wilson, Marjorie (Mrs. Will Wilson), 1956 (1 letter)
  Winde, McCormick & Chapin, 1945 (1 letter)
  Wingler, Hans, undated and 1966-1980 (23 letters): 14 from Breuer; see also Bauhaus Archiv E.V.
  Winkler, Robert, 1955 (1 letter)
  Winsten, Steve, 1968 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Winston, E., 1950 (1 letter)
  Winter, Edward, 1950-1951 (3 letters)
  Wisconsin Chapter of AIA, 1960 (1 letter)
  Wisconsin, University of, 1960 (2 letters)
  Wisdom Encyclopedia, 1966 (1 letter)
  Wogner, Charles, 1951 (2 letters)
  Wohlstetter, Albert (Atlas Aircraft Products Corporation), 1944-1946 (7 letters)
  Wohlstetter, Marjorie, 1946 (1 letter)
  Wolf, Albin, 1933 (5 letters)
  Wolf, Ferenc, 1963-1965 (4 letters)
  Wolfe, James F. (Ketchum, MacLeod & Grove, Inc.), 1960 (2 letters)
  Wolff, Robert Jay, 1956-1975 (3 letters): 1 from Breuer
  Wolfson, Sidney, 1954-1955 (2 letters): from Breuer's office; 1975 letter is from Nicholas P. Appy, executor of Sidney Wolfson's will
  Wollowick, David P., 1947 (1 letter)
  Wong, Andy, 1968 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Wong, Tommy (UCLA), 1974 (1 letter)
  Worcester Art Museum, 1954 (1 letter)
  Working, Jane, undated and 1961 (5 letters)
  Wright, Irving S. and Lois, 1963-1968 (2 letters)
  Wright, Russell (pottery), 1950-1951 (2 letters): from Breuer's office
  Wu, King-lui, 1945-1950 (7 letters): 6 from Breuer
  Wunderlich, Carlos Asensio, 1946 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Wundrich-Meissen, 1934 (1 letter)
  Wurster, William W. (architect) and Catherine, 1946-1960 (6 letters): see American Society of Planners and Architects (ASPA)
  X Functie, 1953-1957 (3 letters)
  Yale University, 1945-1976 (4 letters)
  Yamawaki, Iwao, 1954 (2 letters)
  Yasko, Karel, 1968 (1 letter)
  Yorke, F. R. S. (Francis Reginald Stevens Yorke; architect), 1944-1962 (31 letters)
  Yorke, Thelma and Kay, 1938-1939 (2 letters)
  Yoshimura, Junzo (architect), undated (1 letter): to Yoshimura from Pella Rolscreen Company
  Yoshioka, Yasugoro, undated (1 letter)
  Young, Edward L., 1966 (1 letter)
  Young, Hamilton, 1938 (1 letter)
  Yu, Jane, 1964-1965 (3 letters)
  Yurchenco, Basil ("Chenk"; Goldwater & Yurchenco Associates), 1947-1950 (3 letters)
  Zahedi, H. E. Ardeshir (ambassador of Iran), 1974-1975 (4 letters): from Breuer
  Zanuso, Marco (architect; Olivetti), 1957 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Zechlin, Hans Josef, 1950 (1 letter)
  Ziegler, Barbara, 1947 (1 letter)
  Ziegler, Frank, 1974 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Ziegler, Richard, undated (1 letter)
  Zwick, Virgil J., 1959 (1 letter)
  - Unidentified Correspondents, undated (Box 1, Reel 5708, Frame 600-617)
  - Multiple Correspondents, undated (Box 1, Reel 5708, Frame 618-626)
  - First Names Known, undated, (2 folders) (Box 1, Reel 5708, Frame 627-689)
  - Surnames A-C, undated (Box 1, Reel 5708, Frame 690-793)
  - Surnames D-G, undated (Box 1, Reel 5708, Frame 794-913)
  - Surnames H-J, undated, (3 folders) (Box 1, Reel 5708, Frame 914-998)
  - Surnames K-N, undated (Box 1, Reel 5709, Frame 2-99)
  - Surnames O-Z, undated(oversized material housed in OV 47) (Box 1, Reel 5709, Frame 100-246)
  - Oversized surnames O-Z, undated(oversized material scanned with Box 1, Reel 5709, Frames 100-246) (Box OV 47, Reel 5709)
  - 1923-1926, 1932 (Box 1, Reel 5709, Frame 247-260)
  - January-September 1933 (Box 1, Reel 5709, Frame 261-321)
  - October-December 1933 (Box 1, Reel 5709, Frame 322-370)
  - January-March 1934 (Box 1, Reel 5709, Frame 371-478)
  - April-September 1934 (Box 1, Reel 5709, Frame 479-584)
  - October-December 1934 (Box 1, Reel 5709, Frame 585-639)
  - January-June 1935 (Box 1, Reel 5709, Frame 640-691)
  - July-December 1935 (Box 1, Reel 5709, Frame 692-775)
  - January-July 1936 (Box 1, Reel 5709, Frame 776-857)
  - August-December 1936 (Box 1, Reel 5709, Frame 858-923)
  - January-June 1937 (Box 2, Reel 5709, Frame 924-1006)
  - July-December 1937 (Box 2, Reel 5709, Frame 1007-1076)
  - January-April 1938 (Box 2, Reel 5709, Frame 1077-1114)
  - May-July 1938 (Box 2, Reel 5709, Frame 1115-1168)
  - August-December 1938 (Box 2, Reel 5709, Frame 1169-1226)
  - 1939 (Box 2, Reel 5709, Frame 1227-1278)
  - 1940 (Box 2, Reel 5709, Frame 1279-1302)
  - 1941-1942 (Box 2, Reel 5709, Frame 1303-1321)
  - 1943 (Box 2, Reel 5709, Frame 1322-1370)
  - January-April 1944 (Box 2, Reel 5709, Frame 1371-1416)
  - April-July 1944 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 3-64)
  - August-October 1944 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 65-110)
  - November-December 1944 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 111-182)
  - January-February 1945 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 183-263)
  - March-April 1945 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 264-394)
  - May 1945 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 395-433)
  - June 1945 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 434-483)
  - July-August 1945 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 484-541)
  - September-October 1945 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 542-616)
  - November-December 1945 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 617-668)
  - January-February 1946 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 669-740)
  - March 1946 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 741-804)
  - April 1946 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 805-933)
  - May 1946 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 934-957)
  - June 1946 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 958-1002)
  - July 1946 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 1003-1046)
  - August 1946 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 1047-1097)
  - September 1946 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 1098-1187)
  - October 1946 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 1188-1256)
  - November 1946 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 1257-1301)
  - December 1946 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 1302-1334)
  - January 1947 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 1335-1402)
  - February 1947 (Box 2, Reel 5710, Frame 1403-1416)
  - February 1947 continued (Box 2, Reel 5711, Frame 2-20)
  - March 1947 (Box 2, Reel 5711, Frame 21-52)
  - April 1947 (Box 2, Reel 5711, Frame 53-113)
  - May 1947 (Box 2, Reel 5711, Frame 114-189)
  - June 1947 (Box 2, Reel 5711, Frame 190-240)
  - July 1947 (Box 2, Reel 5711, Frame 241-273)
  - August 1947 (Box 2, Reel 5711, Frame 274-293)
  - September 1947 (Box 2, Reel 5711, Frame 294-359)
  - October 1947 (Box 2, Reel 5711, Frame 360-390)
  - November 1947 (Box 2, Reel 5711, Frame 391-418)
  - December 1947 (Box 2, Reel 5711, Frame 419-462)
  - 1948-1949 (Box 2, Reel 5711, Frame 463-549)
  - January 1950 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 551-618)
  - February 1950 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 619-672)
  - March 1950 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 673-743)
  - April 1950 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 744-774)
  - May 1950 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 775-810)
  - June-July 1950 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 811-845)
  - August-September 1950 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 846-912)
  - October 1950 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 913-945)
  - November 1950 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 946-966)
  - December 1950 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 967-993)
  - January 1951 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 994-1037)
  - February-March 1951 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 1038-1093)
  - April-May 1951 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 1094-1160)
  - June 1951 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 1161-1195)
  - July 1951 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 1196-1216)
  - August 1951 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 1217-1238)
  - September 1951 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 1239-1277)
  - October-November 1951 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 1278-1310)
  - December 1951 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 1311-1331)
  - January-May 1952 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 1332-1355)
  - June-December 1952 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 1356-1395)
  - January-April 1953 (Box 3, Reel 5711, Frame 1396-1422)
  - April-July 1953 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 4-50)
  - August-December 1953 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 51-81)
  - January-February 1954 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 82-125)
  - March 1954 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 126-164)
  - April 1954 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 165-222)
  - May 1954 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 223-250)
  - June 1954 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 251-289)
  - July 1954 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 290-324)
  - August 1954 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 325-354)
  - September 1954 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 355-421)
  - October 1954 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 422-457)
  - November 1954 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 458-517)
  - December 1954 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 518-561)
  - January 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 562-617)
  - February 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 618-640)
  - March 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 641-682)
  - April 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 683-704)
  - May 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 705-741)
  - June 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 742-787)
  - July 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 788-841)
  - August 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 842-893)
  - September 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 894-908)
  - October 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 909-943)
  - November 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 944-971)
  - December 1955 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 972-1004)
  - January 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 1005-1060)
  - February 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 1061-1114)
  - March 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5712, Frame 1115-1169)
  - April 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5713, Frame 4-30)
  - May 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5713, Frame 31-76)
  - June 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5713, Frame 77-110)
  - July 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5713, Frame 111-135)
  - August 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5713, Frame 136-158)
  - September 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5713, Frame 159-195)
  - October 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5713, Frame 196-230)
  - November 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5713, Frame 231-276)
  - December 1956 (Box 3, Reel 5713, Frame 277-331)
  - January 1957 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 332-374)
  - February 1957 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 375-415)
  - March 1957 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 416-462)
  - April 1957 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 463-482)
  - May 1957 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 483-512)
  - June 1957 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 513-538)
  - July 1957 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 539-556)
  - August 1957 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 557-586)
  - September 1957 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 587-605)
  - October 1957 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 606-638)
  - November 1957 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 639-659)
  - December 1957 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 660-684)
  - January 1958 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 685-707)
  - February 1958 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 708-731)
  - March 1958 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 732-758)
  - April 1958 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 759-799)
  - May 1958 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 800-824)
  - June 1958 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 825-848)
  - July 1958 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 849-872)
  - August 1958 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 873-908)
  - September 1958 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 909-943)
  - October 1958 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 944-966)
  - November 1958 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 967-1009)
  - December 1958 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 1010-1045)
  - January 1959 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 1046-1078)
  - February 1959 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 1079-1119)
  - March 1959 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 1120-1152)
  - April 1959 (Box 4, Reel 5713, Frame 1153-1187)
  - May 1959 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 4-43)
  - June 1959 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 44-56)
  - July 1959 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 57-91)
  - August 1959 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 92-102)
  - September 1959 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 103-126)
  - October 1959 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 127-144)
  - November 1959 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 145-190)
  - December 1959 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 191-204)
  - January 1960 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 205-248)
  - February-March 1960 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 249-280)
  - April-May 1960 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 281-310)
  - June 1960 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 311-343)
  - July 1960 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 344-384)
  - August 1960 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 385-423)
  - September 1960 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 424-442)
  - October 1960 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 443-486)
  - November 1960 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 487-525)
  - December 1960 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 526-571)
  - January 1961 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 572-611)
  - February 1961 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 612-631)
  - March 1961 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 632-657)
  - April 1961 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 658-678)
  - May 1961 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 679-689)
  - June 1961 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 690-713)
  - July 1961 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 714-741)
  - August 1961 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 742-756)
  - September 1961 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 757-769)
  - October-December 1961 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 770-783)
  - January 1962 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 784-799)
  - February 1962 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 800-821)
  - March 1962 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 822-834)
  - April 1962 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 835-851)
  - May 1962 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 852-877)
  - June 1962 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 878-897)
  - July 1962 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 898-916)
  - August 1962 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 917-934)
  - September 1962 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 935-970)
  - October 1962 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 971-987)
  - November 1962 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 988-1012)
  - December 1962 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 1013-1038)
  - January 1963 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 1039-1094)
  - February 1963 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 1095-1128)
  - March 1963 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 1129-1172)
  - April 1963 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 1173-1206)
  - May 1963 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 1207-1246)
  - June 1963 (Box 4, Reel 5714, Frame 1247-1275)
  - July 1963 (Box 4, Reel 5715, Frame 4-44)
  - August 1963 (Box 4, Reel 5715, Frame 45-83)
  - September 1963 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 85-148)
  - October 1963 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 149-242)
  - November 1963 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 243-290)
  - December 1963 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 291-315)
  - January 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 316-375)
  - February 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 376-395)
  - March 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 396-412)
  - April 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 413-453)
  - May 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 454-510)
  - June 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 511-562)
  - July 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 563-620)
  - August 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 621-660)
  - September 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 661-704)
  - October 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 705-739)
  - November 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 740-766)
  - December 1964 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 767-821)
  - January 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 822-846)
  - February 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 847-873)
  - March 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 874-932)
  - April 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 933-990)
  - May 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 991-1055)
  - June 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 1056-1080)
  - July 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 1081-1090)
  - August 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 1091-1110)
  - September 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 1111-1128)
  - October 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 1129-1160)
  - November 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 1161-1180)
  - December 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 1181-1195)
  - January 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5715, Frame 1196-1217)
  - February 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 4-37)
  - March 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 38-50)
  - April 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 51-73)
  - May 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 74-89)
  - June 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 90-119)
  - July 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 120-128)
  - August 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 129-146)
  - September 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 147-165)
  - October 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 166-191)
  - November 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 192-248)
  - December 1966 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 249-282)
  - January 1967 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 283-307)
  - February 1967 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 308-343)
  - March 1967 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 344-407)
  - April 1967 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 408-444)
  - May 1967 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 445-461)
  - June 1967 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 462-478)
  - July 1967 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 479-504)
  - August 1967 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 505-520)
  - September 1967 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 521-553)
  - October 1967 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 554-586)
  - November 1967 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 587-616)
  - December 1967 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 617-724)
  - January 1968 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 725-768)
  - February 1968 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 769-832)
  - March 1968 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 833-868)
  - April 1968 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 869-924)
  - May 1968 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 925-959)
  - June 1968 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 960-1026)
  - July 1968 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 1027-1053)
  - August 1968 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 1054-1061)
  - September 1968 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 1062-1077)
  - October 1968 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 1078-1095)
  - November 1968 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 1096-1141)
  - December 1968 (Box 5, Reel 5716, Frame 1142-1164)
  - January-February 1969 (Box 6, Reel 5716, Frame 1165-1185)
  - March 1969 (Box 6, Reel 5716, Frame 1186-1205)
  - April 1969 (Box 6, Reel 5716, Frame 1206-1222)
  - May 1969 (Box 6, Reel 5716, Frame 1223-1245)
  - June 1969 (Box 6, Reel 5716, Frame 1246-1259)
  - July-August 1969 (Box 6, Reel 5716, Frame 1260-1274)
  - September 1969 (Box 6, Reel 5716, Frame 1275-1280)
  - September 1969 continued (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 12-43)
  - October 1969 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 44-111)
  - November-December 1969 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 112-123)
  - January-February 1970 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 124-142)
  - March-April 1970 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 143-150)
  - May-June 1970 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 151-175)
  - July-August 1970 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 176-182)
  - October 1970 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 183-199)
  - November 1970 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 200-258)
  - December 1970 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 259-275)
  - January-February 1971 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 276-287)
  - March-December 1971 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 288-316)
  - January-February 1972 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 317-339)
  - March-July 1972 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 340-364)
  - August 1972 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 365-379)
  - September-December 1972 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 380-394)
  - 1973 (Box 6, Reel 5717, Frame 395-416)